Think nothing of this.
Yau You-fong!
Where's my daughter?
Who are you? Who's your daughter?
My daughter is Sylvia. She's missing.
Says who? Can you prove you're her father?
Look!
Happy birthday, Honey!
Stop filming, Pops!
Just smile...hurry up!
I've been looking for her for a week.
I called her Mom in Taiwan.
She doesn't know where she is.
Tell me where she is.
I'm looking for her too.
Quit your act!
I know you post your PDA online.
She told me you're her boyfriend
and you lied to her.
I caught you with another girl.
Don't bother to deny it.
Calm down. This is my ex-wife.
Rekindling an old flame?
What have you done to my daughter?
I didn't do anything.
Look what she did to us.
Why should I believe you?
How would I know she did this?
Look!
She's mad at Davis because of me.
That's why she took it out on me.
If I didn't recognize the place and
arrived just in time,
Angie could have died.
My daughter is not ruthless.
What exactly happened?
She moved out and didn't tell me where to.
You must know where she is.
I can take you to her studio.
I'll go with you.
After what happened,
you should get some rest.
I'll call you.
Be careful!
Let's go.
Sylvia, open up! I brought your Dad!
Honey, it's me. Open up!
Don't you have the code?
It was 1111, but she changed it.
Here, she has this habit...
She's worried she'll forget the code
or forget the key.
She leaves it outside to be safe.
Sylvia?
Her clothes are gone!
She had me worried sick.
Her passport is gone. She's on the run.
On the run? Why?
You don't know why I needed to
find her so urgently?
She borrowed $1M from a finance company
and I'm her guarantor.
They're after me because
they can't find her.
Wait...she owed $1M?
I thought she had money to spare.
She wanted me to invest with her.
My daughter likes to make quick money.
Last time she borrowed money for
margin trading.
This is the second time she's on the run.
Are you serious?
You said she's been harassing you.
That means she's in Hong Kong.
I'll wait for her right here
and see if she'll come back for her things.
OK! Uncle, call me if you hear from her.
OK...
What are all those contraptions for?
Is she after you?
Did I just see a ghost?
Or was I dreaming?
Why was the TV turned off?
Hello, Angie? Are you still up?
I just woke up from a nightmare.
And you? How's your end?
Did you find Sylvia?
Nobody answered the door.
Uncle found her spare key.
We got in and Sylvia left with her things.
She also took her passport.
She should be on the run.
On the run?
Yes, she's heavily in debt
and the creditor chased Uncle.
No wonder she was anxious for you
to invest with her.
Maybe she needed the money.
That's why when I told her I have
second thoughts about buying overseas,
she threw a fit and forced me
to sell our flat.
Did you discuss how to go forward?
Uncle thinks she's running
from her creditors
He's staying behind
in case Sylvia comes back.
I hope she can sort out her situation
and leave us alone.
Sylvia is unpredictable
and often acts on an impulse.
Be careful when you go out.
OK. You should go to bed. Good night.
Bye.
Oh dear!
Mom, you have anti-allergy meds?
In the cabinet, get it yourself.
We have both topical and oral meds.
What happened to your orchids?
That's what I want to know.
Even if they were to wither,
it should happen slowly and not overnight.
Give me a hair.
To perform black magic?
Did she use black magic on me?
Must find an excuse to lure her out.
Sylvia, I have decided to go ahead
with the investment.
Call me back. Let's talk about this.
You're finally calling me back.
I want to know if you truly want to
be with me,
or you're just worried I'll go after
your beloved Angie
and want to lure me out.
I'm genuinely worried about you.
Your Dad too. He came looking for you
and is now waiting in your studio.
He said you're in debt.
Why can't he mind his own business?
I know you reacted like this
because of money.
Why don't I borrow money for you?
Please stop doing this.
Don't harass or hurt Angie anymore, OK?
You think I'm with you because of money?
You're willing to lend me money
all because of Angie.
No. I genuinely want to help you.
Let's meet and talk.
It's better to put two minds together.
Don't bother.
You'll just discuss it with your ex again.
You know what really pissed me off?
It's not the money. But because
you lied to me.
Sylvia, you got this all wrong.
You love her that much?
OK. Get ready to be star-crossed lovers.
Hello? Sylvia...
Mom, knock before you come in!
What about my privacy?
No matter, you're my son.
Let's not get into that.
I want to ask you,
is Sylvia harassing you and Angie?
You were eavesdropping?
Would you tell me if I didn't?
I knew that witch is bad news.
I was right all along.
You can't blame her. It was my fault.
Don't feel guilty. She set you up, son.
The day you fell off the hillside,
I visited you at the hospital.
Naturally, I looked in on Angie as well.
I found out it was Angie
who saved your life.
(five months before)
You're in worse shape than Davis!?
Don't worry, Auntie. I'm fine.
Back then, Davis passed out
and it was dangerous on the slope.
I wanted to go get help,
but I was worried to leave
Davis by himself out there.
I pulled him up to somewhere flat.
But I was a klutz and fell back down...
So you saved Davis?
Were you strong enough?
Auntie, remember you drew a lot for us?
I was thinking...
if we stick with each other
and won't give up,
we can overcome anything.
Then I suddenly felt full of energy...
That's amazing.
How could you laugh about it?
Why didn't you tell Davis you saved him
and let him think the witch did?
It doesn't matter.
I didn't do it to make him feel grateful.
Besides, he seems to hit it off with Sylvia.
They're so sweet and he's so in love.
It doesn't matter if I tell him or not.
Your ex risked her life to save yours.
But this witch is hurting you.
See? Your skin is sensitive
and you hurt your hands.
I think she's definitely behind it.
I don't know how you can get away.
I better ask Uncle Kim what we can do.
Angie!
Get in. I'll take you to work.
Why all of a sudden?
You leave at 9:30 a.m.?
Yes. Why?
I'm worried Sylvia will
come after you again.
I figure I'll take you to and from work, OK?
OK. But won't that impose on you?
I took time off. I spoke to the Boss.
I didn't want my personal life to
affect my work.
He told me to take two weeks off.
I need to clear my annual leave anyway.
You're going to stick with me 24 x 7?
I'm not going back to the office today.
Where are you going?
I'm doing research in a walled village.
I don't want you to be alone.
Get in. I'll drop you.
Sylvia finally called me back.
I told her I'll borrow money for her
but she bit my head off.
She still thinks we got back together
behind her back.
There's nothing we can do
if she doesn't believe you.
Looks like she's still emotionally unstable.
Has she been harassing you?
No. But you can't pick me up every day
and stick with me.
We'll play by ear.
At least try to reduce your chance
of being alone.
But if she can harass us through the air,
we must find a way to defend ourselves.
There's still another way.
Such as?
I plan to leave Hong Kong.
Are you running from Sylvia?
She's behaving like this because
she got the wrong idea about us.
If I leave, she'll get over it
and she'll leave you alone.
Of course not!
There's no reason you should suffer
the consequences.
You said you like Hong Kong.
You shouldn't have to leave.
OK...it was just an idea.
I'm working on a new program,
I can't leave yet.
I'll think about it later.
Here we are.
This new program I'm doing
is about the history and culture
of a walled village.
I'm meeting the person in charge out here.
She'll show me around.
I should go. Thank you.
I'll go with you.
OK!
Mom told me last time we fell down the slope
it was you who pulled me back up.
But all along, I thought it was Sylvia.
It doesn't matter who actually saved you.
What matters is you're fine.
Of course not!
Mom consulted a fortune teller,
whoever goes through thick and thin
with me is my true love.
If that's the case, when I was injured,
the real person who saved me is crucial.
Are you Miss Man?
Auntie Mui, we're working on a program
called Historical Places.
It features the local customs and
history of this place.
You came to the right person.
My family has been living here
for several generations.
We help Mr. Chow look after the mansion.
You can film inside,
but make sure you don't lose anything.
Or else Mr. Chow will scold me
when he returns from overseas.
Don't worry!
We'll try not to touch anything.
Good. Follow me.
OK!
This mansion has a long history
that has passed through several generations.
This is the courtyard.
My mother was a servant.
When I was little,
I loved listening to her telling
stories of this place,
especially about Mr. Chow.
You said this place was passed down
for many generations,
what period did Mr. Chow live in?
Probably 100 years ago.
During the early days of the Republic?
Yes.
I'll show you the master bedroom.
Great.
Mother told me Mr. Chow lived here
after he got married.
But only for a short time.
Nobody has lived here ever since.
What? You have seen the wedding gown before?
I think so.
Auntie Mui, why did the owner,
I mean Mr. Chow
leave the wedding gown here?
I told you last time you were here.
Nobody left it hanging.
I wasn't here last time.
Don't deny it.
If you're forgetful, do what Ms. Man did,
jot it down in a notebook.
Right...I'm forgetful.
Can you tell me again?
OK.
Mother said the wedding gown
belonged to one of the servants.
She was getting married
but the groom broke off the engagement
and she died wearing the wedding gown.
Why leave this ominous gown hanging there?
That's just it...everyone saw the girl
buried in the gown.
On the seventh day after the girl died,
people in the mansion saw the gown
hanging in this room.
Later on, whoever tried to take
the gown away,
something bad would happen.
They either tripped and fell, hurt
their hands or bumped their heads.
In the end, no one dared touch it again
and just left it hanging there.
That's spooky.
Of course it is!
The girl was mean and nasty.
When she found out her fiance dumper her,
she picked up an axe
and hacked the tree under which
they pledged their love.
She almost chopped it down.
Bye!
When Auntie Mui was telling us the story
about that girl,
you were entranced. What were you thinking?
Nothing. Sylvia's Dad contacted me
and told me more about her past.
What did he say?
She's rather self-centered and moody.
Anything goes when she likes something,
but when she doesn't like it,
she'll go crazy.
No wonder she tried to come between us.
There's more...he said one time
her boyfriend wanted to break up with her,
she was so pissed she showed up
at his house...
Hey!
Come on, Honey!
The guy is not right for you.
Forget him. Find someone else.
Forget him?
Come on...
I won't let it slide.
Honey...
Out of my way!
Let's go...
You come any closer, I'll hack you too.
That's why when Auntie Mui said
after the girl's fiance broke off
the engagement,
she hacked the tree,
I remember when Sylvia's boyfriend
cheated on her,
she hacked his door.
They both hacked something with an axe.
Am I making it sound too scary?
Maybe I'm overthinking.
Remember I told you
since Sylvia started harassing us,
I often had nightmares?
Once, a girl wearing a Chinese wedding gown
flashed in front of my eyes.
I couldn't decide if I was dreaming,
or it was real.
But I remember the wedding gown
she was wearing,
was very similar to the one hanging in
Mr. Chow's room.
What a coincidence!
Sylvia and that girl had things in common.
You were doing this new program
and stumbled up the wedding gown.
Somehow, things are connected.
Is Sylvia somehow connected to this place?
We better believe it.
Like Mom said, we may need the help
of a professional.
Uncle Kim, this is more than bad luck
in romance.
How can we resolve this?
Don't worry, let me try to understand
this better.
You just said Sylvia's behavior
was very similar to that girl
from the mansion.
Other than using an axe,
what else is very similar?
Maybe not.
I asked Sylvia's Dad,
he can't seem to put his finger on
how Sylvia was connected to
the walled village.
That's why we think it may be
just a coincidence.
Nothing in this world is a coincidence.
We call it a coincidence because
we have yet to uncover the profundity
or its cause and effect.
Remember how you first came across
the mansion in the walled village?
A friend of mine dragged me to
pray to the Lover's Rock.
After that, we threw a wishing placard
onto the wishing tree.
Are you ready to go?
Don't run after it. Throw another one.
I had a feeling when I saw the mansion.
I was thinking about doing a program
like Historical Places.
I wanted to see if it's doable.
So I asked the caretaker, Auntie Mui
to let me take a peek inside.
She told me Mr. Chow, the owner of
the mansion is very rich.
I walked past Mr. Chow's bedroom
but I didn't go inside,
and didn't notice the wedding gown.
Until we decided to do the show,
I interviewed Auntie Mui again
and I recognized the wedding gown.
It was the same as the one I saw
in my dream or in an illusion.
At first, I thought since this mansion
has such a long history,
there should be plenty of stories to tell.
That's why I took on this project.
But it never dawned on me
the story behind is much more
complicated than I thought.
The gown you saw...whether in a dream
or an illusion
was exactly the same?
Or just a similar style?
No.
The embroidery was very special.
That's why I'm sure it was the same one.
That's really scary and bizarre.
When the maid and Sylvia were dumped,
they both hacked something with an axe.
After Sylvia harassed you,
you saw the wedding gown.
When the dog led you to the mansion,
you saw the gown in Mr. Chow's room.
The course of nature went around
and determined the chance of
you three meeting each other.
The chance of Angie seeing the gown
and finding the mansion
proved you have an indissoluble bond
with this place.
The grudge Sylvia holds against you
should be more than out of jealousy.
That witch is vicious, it's definitely
bad karma.
How can we resolve this?
You can't.
No way to resolve it?
Uncle Kim, you told me in the past,
anything can be resolved.
He's my only child,
you must think of a way to help him.
Unless you avoid her completely
and go as far away as possible.
Actually I have considered
emigrating overseas.
Don't be reckless.
This is just our wild guess.
If you want to find out more,
I know someone who can help you.
Is hypnosis difficult?
Usually, you only need to relax.
Are you ready?
OK, close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
Try your best to relax
and release all your pressure.
Slowly raise your right hand.
Imagine you're holding a bucket
and water is slowly filling up the bucket.
As the water is filling up,
the bucket becomes heavy.
Then I would count from one to three.
On my count to three,
let your subconscious go as far as possible.
1...2...3...
(Chow's Mansion)
Where's Ning-yuk's bridal sedan chair?
Master, it's not yet the auspicious hour.
Be patient.
Why did we stop?
A jinx is in the way.
Don't talk nonsense! Who is it?
Master Chow has a child bride
called On-yee.
She's getting married on the same day.
I don't think so. She did this on purpose.
The child bride was sold to the Chow family
when she was little.
She thought she'd marry the young master
when she grew up.
But you're marrying the young master,
and the young master also found her
a suitable husband.
But this child bride held a grudge
and wanted revenge.
What do you mean, Master Sin?
It's a taboo for a wedding to clash
with another wedding.
Now we have two brides getting married
on the same day
and the bridal sedan chairs clashed.
When two happy occasions clashed,
it will bring bad luck.
At best, the marriage will break up.
Worse yet, there will be bloodshed.
If Master Sin says so,
Ling-yee, we should let them through.
OK.
Porter, let's go around.
Early years of the Republic?
That was over 100 years ago.
You recognize any of those people?
I don't recognize any of them.
But Master Chow and his bride
gave me a feeling of deja vu.
If that's the case,
the servant Auntie Mui mentioned
should be the child bride.
She's too barbaric.
How can we resolve the situation?
How can we do that?
Davis, what are you thinking?
I'm thinking...
if I could piece back
together the whole story
and find out more about our
connections with Master Chow...
Too bad I was too nervous.
The hypnotist said I wasn't relaxed enough
and couldn't get into a hypnotic state.
Davis, you just said if
you were Master Chow...
Does that mean there's a chance you're not?
I don't know.
Maybe because we didn't see it
with our own eyes,
that's why just like you,
we have the feeling of deja vu.
There's actually another way.
Now we know about Master Chow's mansion
and the Chows have descendants.
That means someone should know
what happened back then.
Inside the walled village, we should
be able to find...
information on Master Chow and Miss Koo.
Let's go inside the walled village again.
You're doing research with me?
I made copies of the genealogy
of the Chow clan
and some old photos.
You can take these with you.
Thank you, Chief.
You're welcome. Let me know
when the show goes on air.
No problem.
I should get going.
OK. Thank you.
Bye!
It's definitely him.
Master Chow looked exactly like him.
And all these paintings?
Master Chow drew them.
The village Chief said his name was Kai-hin.
That means these were all his paintings.
But these are oil paintings.
Maybe he studied overseas
and learnt Western painting
just like Xu Beihong and Wu Zuoren
went to France to learn painting,
sketching and oil painting.
This is similar to your paintings.
Look! I found Master Chow's diary.
Thanks, Auntie Mui.
Where have I seen you before?
I'll leave you alone. Help yourselves.
I'll go prepare dinner.
OK. Thanks, Auntie Mui.
It's more than a diary.
There are recipes inside.
But the handwriting is different.
It looks like the handwriting of a woman.
I remember Master Chow's wife's
last name is Koo.
Koo Ning-yuk should have written
these recipes.
I didn't realize Miss Koo
was a good cook like you.
And like you, Master Chow liked to paint
and preferred Western sketching
which was uncommon back then.
And he loved drawing his wife
very much too.
When I was hypnotized,
I saw the wishing tree.
It should be the one hacked by
the child bride.
The marks are still here
after all these years.
People didn't know what to do.
The tree didn't heal.
That's why there are scars.
Master Chow and Miss Koo owed her nothing.
Maybe the child bride only behaved
in a fit of rage.
Just think, Sylvia lied to you
from the start.
When you discovered the lie
and you broke up with her,
she began her revenge.
Auntie Mui said the child bride
died in that wedding gown,
which means she was full of
resentment and remorse...
Angie, I know what you're worried about.
She clashed the wedding
but she also died from it.
Maybe that was her retribution.
And it didn't affect Master Chow
and Miss Koo.
But the question is
we don't know what happened to
Master Chow and Miss Koo.
No. I should leave Hong Kong ASAP.
The sooner she gets over it,
she won't hurt you anymore.
Angie...don't go.
I don't want you to leave me.
I don't care about Sylvia's background
or what she'll do to us.
I will stick with you and protect you.
Angie, we should get back together.
Davis, we acted on an impulse once.
Besides, so much has happened lately.
I think we should calm down first
and think things over later, OK?
Liz...
How are you?
Auntie said she's worried about you.
You haven't eaten or gone out
in the past few days.
Are you sick?
Did you have a fight with Roy?
Don't talk about him.
How are you lately?
I'm OK. Davis has been with me lately.
You should stay away from him.
He'll get you killed.
Didn't you say you want to leave?
Stop dragging your feet.
He wants me to stay.
Stay? Why?
You want to get back together with him?
That guy can't be trusted.
What spell did he cast on you?
You tried it once and it didn't work.
He won't change.
I think he has changed.
He's more sincere compared to before.
You're hopeless.
You fell under his charm and
changed your tune.
I have nothing to say to you. Just go.
Liz...how unusual of you to ask me out.
Only because of Angie.
Or else, I don't want to see you.
I urge you to let go.
This is between Angie and me.
You have the right to decide.
Angie simply can't get over you.
If she continues to stick with you,
she'll just get hurt again.
You and I both care about Angie.
I can assure you, I won't hurt her again.
I will protect her and take care of her.
If you could do that,
you wouldn't have gotten a divorce.
You're a player, Angie is a homebody.
I beg you to continue to be
your legless bird.
Give Angie a chance to meet a decent man.
Then we can all feel better.
Do you know why there's an eraser
on a pencil?
Because people make mistakes.
Mistakes can be atoned.
Give us another chance, OK?
(There was a man)
(That sailed the seas)
(He left his woman)
(behind to leave)
(He kissed his children)
(And turned to go)
(And don't you cry)
I told you the Observatory predicted
rain for today.
Luckily, it didn't get wet.
(I'm coming home)
(There was a ship)
(That sailed the seas)
What are you painting?
The leaves are not in full bloom.
No, they look very pretty.
Wow! That's pretty. When did you finish?
I know I can't promise you anything.
When you start something, it's best
to carry through the end.
We don't know how this will end.
I know you like things well-planned
and you need a sense of security.
Last time I wanted to paint
the leaves out here,
you knew the Observatory predicted rain
and still came with me.
But we didn't finish the painting.
Who would have guessed before
we left home today,
we actually checked the weather report.
I guess we should finish the painting today.
I'm quite sure
I don't want this moment to be the end.
Just like the lot Mom drew for us,
if we stick together and don't give up,
we can overcome anything.
Angie, promise me,
let's get back together?
We can tackle any problem.
(Don't you cry)
(He's coming home)
Sir, Siu Zi-yiu has been harassing us
for quite some time.
My ex-wife and I have been wounded.
I don't know how she did it.
She gave us rashes and bruises.
We want to speak to her but
can't find her.
Can you find her for us?
Mr. Yau, we opened a file for you.
We'll conduct an investigation based on
the information you provided.
If you hear anything, please contact us.
You've been investigating long enough.
What have you found out?
We're working on it.
For you to come to the
Police station every day
will only get in our way.
I'm in your way?
When will your investigation end?
Don't worry. We'll call you
if we hear anything.
Don't worry?
Uncle...any word on Sylvia?
Yes!
Sylvia appeared in my dream.
She said it was hot and stuffy where she is.
I'm Kwan Zhi-fung of the Crime Unit
in New Territories East.
Are you Mr. Siu Bong-chak?
Sir, did something happen to my daughter?
The MPU found her car in the mountains.
The Police found the last image
of Sylvia's car
on the CCTV from two weeks ago.
We traced the route
and found the car in the mountains.
We also found blood in the car
and this small wheel,
which we suspect came off a suitcase.
According to the hematology test,
we confirmed it was Siu Zi-yiu's blood.
Hold on...are you saying Sylvia
might have died two weeks ago?
I'm sorry, who are you?
I'm her ex-boyfriend.
Kwan Sir...Mr. Yau said Siu Zi-yiu
has been harassing him and his ex-wife
for the past two weeks.
But he hasn't been able to find her.